http://www.citizentribune.com/site/privacy.html

12 hrs ago
A predawn fire that broke out in the exterior dust-control system at Jones Fiber Products on Pope Road in East Morristown halted production early this morning, a work stoppage that persisted into late morning, according to Brian Shepard, deputy chief of the Morristown Fire Department.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Teen killed in Jefferson County crash
Planning commission discusses Suboxone clinic
Harrell battles COVID-19, twice
Widow turns to Holiday Hope Fund for support
Grainger men sentenced in rapes
City of Morristown to host MEDIC blood drive Dec. 11
12 hrs ago
A predawn fire that broke out in the exterior dust-control system at Jones Fiber Products on Pope Road in East Morristown halted production early this morning, a work stoppage that persisted into late morning, according to Brian Shepard, deputy chief of the Morristown Fire Department.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Teen killed in Jefferson County crash
Planning commission discusses Suboxone clinic
Harrell battles COVID-19, twice
Widow turns to Holiday Hope Fund for support
Grainger men sentenced in rapes
City of Morristown to host MEDIC blood drive Dec. 11
12 hrs ago
Greg Harrell considers himself lucky.
Read more
More Headlines
State health departments to dial back testing, gear up for vaccinations
School board talks COVID enrollment
Hamblen sees largest single day increase
Lee says he will get virus vaccination when ‘time is right’
State health department updates quarantine procedures
Sports
2020 Citizen Tribune Classic
2020 Fall School Sports Schedule
Local Sports
National Sports
Pro32: Head to Head
NCAA Basketball
15 hrs ago
JEFFERSON CITY – Braelyn Wykle led all scorers with an efficient 29 points and Carson-Newman won the battle on the glass in a 75-62 victory over Anderson Wednesday evening at Holt Fieldhouse in South Atlantic Conference play.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
Henson, Simpson selected to stateoftennesseehsfb.com All-State football team
Jeff Co. girls struggle after hot start
East hangs on for tough conference win over Sevier County
Lady Grizz overcome slow start to take down Lady Bulldogs
Undefeated Sevier County too much for Lady ‘Canes
Overbay sparks Grainger in win over Claiborne
Offense struggles as West falls to South Doyle
Double-digit losses piling up for Tennessee
Living
Nov 29, 2020
Three children of the Slover family recently celebrated birthdays.
Read All Announcements
More Announcements
Lowder - Carson exchange vows
Beachs celebrate 60th anniversary
Goforths mark 50th anniversary
Birth Announcements
Rossies hold baby shower
Lane - Rhoton to exchange vows
Arts & Entertainment
UT Theatre Department presents Capote's ‘A Christmas Memory’
From Contributed Reports
Dec 6, 2020
The University of Tennessee Department of Theatre presents Truman Capote’s “A Christmas Memory,” read by Carol Mayo Jenkins, recorded on location at the Mabry Hazen House, and directed by John Sipes. The free, streaming recording is available NOW through Dec. 25. In conjunction with the read…
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
New light spectacular at Zoo Knoxville for the holidays
Jingle Run goes virtual
Rose Center to host Artists Sunday, Nov. 29
Abbott’s latest movie opens in theatres and online
Dollywood’s Smoky Mountain Christmas wraps families in the light of the season
Legacy Theatre to present ‘A Christmas Carol - a Radio Play’
Dollywood’s Harvest Festival feels fresh yet familiar
Country star and hit Elvis songwriter Mac Davis dies at 78
Features
Home Improvement
Health & Wellness
Money & Finance
Beauty & Fitness
Food & Recipes
Online Features
How Hackers Could Use the Pandemic and Technology Against Us in 2021 [Video]
Brandpoint (BPT)
Dec 9, 2020
Sorry, but your browser does not support the video tag.
Read All Headlines
More Headlines
5 ways to experience wine country from home
Sculpt Your Best Body Now: Get Trim and Toned with This Advanced Duo Treatment
Need more functionality? 4 simple ways to upgrade your laundry room
Experiencing Constipation? Make a New Year’s Resolution to Get the Help You Need
Sleep-trainer approved tips for new parents
Fall prevention: Tips to enjoy favorite winter activities safely
BookBites: Four Diverse Stories To Intrigue Readers
Create a plan: Working with a doctor to help manage a chronic inflammatory condition
Classifieds
Search All Classifieds
Place a Classified Ad
Public Notices
TN Public Notices
Garage & Yard Sales
Announcements
Services
14 hrs ago
Ada Belle Rhea, 81, of Bean Station, passed away peacefully Monday, December 7, 2020. She was a member of Adriel Missionary Baptist Church, and a beloved librarian at Bean Station Library for many years.
Read All Obituaries
More Obituaries
Yvonne DeCarol Treece McAdams
Grant H. Gibson
Milburn Wayne Gibson
Ronald Emmitt Weston
Sammy Price
Ada Belle Rhea
Dec 10, 2020
Take a look at this 3 bed, 2 bath, spacious home located just outside of Greeneville, with a super short drive to the city! Enjoy the beautiful mountain views that can be seen from every room in the home, or cuddle up by the wood burning fire place in the living room and watch your favorite …
See All Real Estate
More Real Estate
Lot 12 Majestic Cr, Dandridge, TN 37725
3287 Hwy 411, Dandridge, TN 37725
6571 E Andrew Johnson Hwy, Whitesburg, TN 37891
440 Lochmere Drive, Morristown, TN 37814-2186
140 Ellis St, Bean Station, TN 37708
1116 Plum Ct, Talbott, TN 37877
786 Lakewood, Jefferson City, TN 37760
Lot 4 CH Rankin, White Pine, TN 37890-9999
Lakeway Area Jobs
Lakeway Publishers, Inc. d.b.a. Citizen Tribune, (Citizen Tribune), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Citizen Tribune of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.THEREFOREthis Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Citizen Tribune , and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.citizentribune.com you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.Collection of InformationThis website collects various types of information, such as:Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.In addition to our own cookies, we may also allow various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the service and deliver targeted advertisements and content on and through the service.Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.Citizen Tribune may have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion at a later time.We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.Use of Information CollectedCitizen Tribune may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.citizentribune.com . Citizen Tribune  may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.Citizen Tribune does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.Citizen Tribune may feel it necessary, from time to time, to make contact with you on behalf of other external business partners with regards to a potential new offer which may be of interest to you. If you consent or show interest in presented offers, then, at that time, specific identifiable information, such as name, email address and/or telephone number, may be shared with the third party.Citizen Tribune may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.Citizen Tribune may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Citizen Tribune and/or our website;Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Citizen Tribune; andPerform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.citizentribune.com and/or the general public.Children Under Age of 13Citizen Tribune does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.Unsubscribe or Opt-OutAll users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to [Need Email]. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.Links to Other Web SitesOur website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Citizen Tribune does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.SecurityCitizen Tribune shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.Third Party AdvertisersWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please complete the following links:   http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp,   http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.Changes to Privacy Policy AgreementCitizen Tribune reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at www.citizentribune.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Citizen Tribune decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.Acceptance of TermsThrough the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.Email:info@citizentribune.comTelephone Number: 423-581-5630Mailing Address:Citizen Tribune1609 W. 1st N. StreetMorristown, Tennessee 3781402/27/2017
Latest News
US-Pres-Sum,100
US carries out rare execution during presidential transition
The Latest: South Korea expanding virus testing, tracing
MetLife Announces New $3 Billion Share Repurchase Authorization
Global Conference Spurred Large Influx of Investment to Shenzhen
MetLife to Sell Auto & Home Business to Zurich Insurance Group Subsidiary Farmers Group, Inc. for $3.94 Billion
US-House-Sum,100
US-Senate-Sum,100
Weekly Poll
How much Christmas shopping have you completed so far?
You voted:
I haven't even begun, so 0%.
I'm about half done, still have to order a few things, so 50%.
I'm nearly done. Stocking stuffers is all I still need. 90%.
Christmas shopping? What Christmas shopping?
Vote
View Results
Back
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesCocke County man pleads guilty to rape and incestFatal Crash in New MarketHamblen sees largest single day increaseFather crashes on I-40 after kicked in head by sonMan revived in Cocke County JailWalter Coffey, West High’s No. 1 fan, diesMan dies after van falls during burglary attemptHarrell battles COVID-19, twiceTeen killed in Jefferson County crashCommunity leader and philanthropist Linda Dietrich dies
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
© Copyright 2020 Citizen Tribune, 1609 W. 1st N. Street Morristown, TN | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
Notifications
Settings
You don't have any notifications.
Get up-to-the-minute news sent straight to your device.
Daily Devotional (KJV)
School Closings - Claiborne Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Cocke Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Lakeway Christian
Subscribe
School Closings - Grainger Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Hamblen Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Hancock Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Hawkins Co.
Subscribe
School Closings - Jefferson Co.
Sports Scores - Claiborne Co.
Subscribe
Sports Scores - Cocke Co.
Subscribe
Sports Scores - Grainger Co.
Sports Scores - Hancock Co.
Subscribe
Sports Scores - Hawkins Co.
Subscribe
Sports Scores - Jefferson Co.
